Saving the day the monster way.
Monsters vs Aliens is a animation, family,
adventure film directed by Rob Letterman.
When Susan Murphy is unwittingly clobbered by a meteor full of outer space gunk
on her wedding day, she mysteriously grows to 49-feet-11-inches.
The military jumps into action and captures Susan, secreting
her away to a covert government compound.
She is renamed Ginormica and placed in confinement
with a ragtag group of Monsters...
Susan Murphy / Ginormica (voice), played by Reese Witherspoon.
B.O.B. (voice), played by Seth Rogen.
Dr. Cockroach Ph.D. (voice), played by Hugh Laurie.
Gallaxhar (voice), played by Rainn Wilson.
The Missing Link (voice), played by Will Arnett.
General W.R. Monger (voice), played by Kiefer Sutherland.
Monsters vs.
Aliens is a 2009 American animated science fiction comedy film directed by Conrad Vernon and Rob Letterman
and written by Letterman, Maya Forbes, Wally Wolodarsky, Jonathan Aibel and Glenn Berger.
Produced by DreamWorks Animation, it is the first
installment in the Monsters vs.
Aliens franchise.
The film stars Reese Witherspoon, Seth Rogen, Hugh Laurie, Will Arnett,
Kiefer Sutherland, Rainn Wilson, Paul Rudd, and Stephen Colbert.
The film involves a group of misfit monsters tasked by the United States Armed Forces to stop the
invasion of an extraterrestrial villain and save the Earth in exchange for freedom.
It was DreamWorks Animation's first feature film to be produced in a stereoscopic 3D format instead of
being converted into 3D after completion, which added $15 million to the film's budget.
Monsters vs.
Aliens was released in the United States on March 27, 2009, by
Paramount Pictures, to mixed reviews from critics.
It was a box-office success, grossing $381 million on a $175 million budget.
It was followed by two television specials, Mutant Pumpkins from Outer Space and
Night of the Living Carrots, and a television series in 2013.
The film explores themes of monster, villain, alien,
giant robot, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.